http://www.laurelhighlands.com/privacy-policy/

Gift Cards
Privacy PolicyWhat information do we collect?We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:; To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs); To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you); To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs); To send periodic emailsThe email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.How do we protect your information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.Do we use cookies?Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain informationWe use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceBecause we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.Your ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.Laurel Highlands River Tours and Outdoor CenterLaurel Highlands Outdoor Center 4 Sherman Street Ohiopyle, PA 15470 Phone: 1-800-4RAFTIN (1-800-472-3846) Local: 724-329-8531 Fax: 724-329-8532 Email: 4raftin@laurelhighlands.com
Booking
Specials
Packages
Buy Photos
Gift Cards Sign Up Today for Great Specials!
Laurel Highlands River Tours & Outdoor Center4 Sherman StreetOhiopyle, PA 15470724-329-8531info@laurelhighlands.comFrom Our Blog Enjoy fall in Ohiopyle: Bike the great Allegheny Passage. Tripadvisor’s Travelers’ Choice Award Winner 2020 We are OPENING! Visit BlogMore InfoGroup Organizer InfoArea AttractionsFAQRiver Class GuideMapsLiability Forms
Laurel Highlands River Tours & Outdoor Center ©2020. All Rights ReservedSitemap | Privacy Policy Scroll Up
